export const topick7 = [
  {
    question:
      'What type of fishing was predominant in Ostend in the 17th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Cod fishing',
      b: 'Salmon fishing',
      c: 'Herring fishing',
    },
    answer: 'Cod fishing',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What type of fish was the main export of Ostend in the 18th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Cod',
      b: 'Salmon',
      c: 'Herring',
    },
    answer: 'Herring',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the first fish market in Ostend founded?',
    options: {
      a: '1604',
      b: '1722',
      c: '1830',
    },
    answer: '1722',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What marine animal was the main object of fishing in Ostend in the 19th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Shrimp',
      b: 'Octopus',
      c: 'Crabs',
    },
    answer: 'Shrimp',
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of fishing was popular in Ostend in the 18th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Deep sea fishing',
      b: 'Coastal fishing',
      c: 'Commercial fishing',
    },
    answer: 'Coastal fishing',
  },
  {
    question:
      "What product was the main export of Ostend's fishing industry in the 19th century?",
    options: {
      a: 'Cod',
      b: 'Herring',
      c: 'Shrimp',
    },
    answer: 'Shrimp',
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year was the first fishing port in Ostend opened?',
    options: {
      a: '1670',
      b: '1725',
      c: '1838',
    },
    answer: '1838',
  },
  {
    question: 'What vessel was used for fishing in Ostend in the 18th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Barquentine',
      b: 'Schooner',
      c: 'Galley',
    },
    answer: 'Galley',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What type of fish was the most popular at the fish market of Ostend in the 19th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Herring',
      b: 'Salmon',
      c: 'Cod',
    },
    answer: 'Herring',
  },
  {
    question:
      'What trade was the main occupation for the fishermen of Ostend in the 18th century?',
    options: {
      a: 'Crab fishing',
      b: 'Shrimp fishing',
      c: 'Cod fishing',
    },
    answer: 'Cod fishing',
  },
];
